The Stanford marshmallow test was originally conducted by psychologist Walter Mischel in the late 1960s.
斯坦福棉花糖实验最初是由心理学家沃尔特·米舍尔在20世纪60年代末进行的。
Children aged four to six at a nursery school were placed in a room.
一所幼儿园里四到六岁的孩子被安排在一个房间里。
A single sugary treat, selected by the child, was placed on a table.
桌子上放了一块由孩子自己挑选的甜食。
Each child was told that if they waited for 15 minutes before eating the treat, they would be given a second treat.
每个孩子都被告知：如果等15分钟再吃这块甜食，就会得到第二块甜食。
Then they were left alone in the room.
然后，他们被单独留在房间里。
Follow-up studies with the children later in life showed a connection between an ability to wait long enough to obtain a second treat and various forms of success.
日后对这些孩子进行的跟踪研究表明，为获得第二块甜食而等待足够长时间的能力，与各种形式的成功之间存在关联。
As adults we face a version of the marshmallow test every day.
作为成年人，我们每天都要面对某种形式的棉花糖实验。
We’re tempted not by sugary treats but by our computers, phones, and tablets — all the devices that connect us to the global delivery system for various types of information that do to us what marshmallows do to preschoolers.
诱惑我们的不是甜食，而是我们的电脑、手机和平板电脑——所有这些设备把我们与传送各类信息的全球系统连接起来，而这些信息对我们的作用，就如同棉花糖对学龄前儿童的作用。
We are tempted by sugary treats because our ancestors lived in a calorie-poor world, and our brains developed a response mechanism to these treats that reflected their value — a feeling of reward and satisfaction.
我们之所以受甜食诱惑，是因为我们的祖先生活在一个热量匮乏的世界里，而我们的大脑对这类食物形成了一种能体现其价值的反应机制——一种奖赏感和满足感。
But as we’ve reshaped the world around us, dramatically reducing the cost and effort involved in obtaining calories, we still have the same brains we had thousands of years ago, and this mismatch is at the heart of why so many of us struggle to resist tempting foods that we know we shouldn’t eat.
然而，尽管我们已经重塑了周围的世界，大大减少了获取热量所需的成本和精力，我们的大脑却仍和几千年前一样；这种不匹配，正是我们当中这么多人明知有些诱人的食物不该吃、却难以抗拒的根本原因。
A similar process is at work in our response to information.
我们对信息的反应中也有类似的过程在起作用。
Our formative environment as a species was information-poor, so our brains developed a mechanism that prized new information.
作为一个物种，我们在形成时期所处的环境信息匮乏，因此大脑发展出了一种重视新信息的机制。
But global connectivity has greatly changed our information environment.
然而，全球互联已经极大地改变了我们的信息环境。
We are now ceaselessly bombarded with new information.
如今，我们不断受到新信息的狂轰滥炸。
Therefore, just as we need to be more thoughtful about our caloric consumption, we also need to be more thoughtful about our information consumption, resisting the temptation of the mental “junk food” in order to manage our time most effectively.
因此，正如我们需要更加审慎地对待热量摄入一样，我们也需要更加审慎地对待信息摄入，抵制精神“垃圾食品”的诱惑，以便最有效地管理我们的时间。